<dashboard version="1.1">
  <label>Help</label>
  <row>
    <html><h1>REST storage/passwords Manager for Splunk</h1>

<h2>About</h2>
<p>An intuitive, full-featured JavaScript CRUD interface to the <a href="https://docs.splunk.com/Documentation/Splunk/latest/RESTREF/RESTaccess#storage.2Fpasswords">Splunk storage/passwords REST endpoint</a>. Create, update, delete, and view credentials — plus manage permissions, sharing scope, and app context — all from a single dashboard.</p>

<h2>Dependencies</h2>
<p>To store passwords a user must have the <code>admin_all_objects</code> capability enabled within an assigned role. To read passwords a user must have the <code>list_storage_passwords</code> capability enabled within an assigned role. Grant <code>list_storage_passwords</code> carefully — users with this capability can view credentials across any app where they have read access.</p>

<h2>Usage</h2>
<p>The <strong>Credential Management</strong> dashboard provides a CRUD interface to create, update, and delete credentials.</p>

<h4>Create Credential</h4>
<p>Click <strong>+ New Credential</strong> to reveal the creation form. Fill in a username, password, and optionally a realm (a descriptor such as <code>prod</code> or <code>dev</code>). The form pre-fills with secure defaults for owner, read users, write users, app scope, and sharing — update them before clicking <strong>Create</strong>.</p>

<h4>Update Credential</h4>
<p>Click any row in the table to expand it and reveal the inline update form. You can change the password, permissions, or app context. The realm cannot be changed after creation — this is a limitation of the <code>storage/passwords</code> REST endpoint, not the app.</p>

<h4>Delete Credential</h4>
<p>Select one or more rows using the checkboxes in the left column, then click <strong>Delete</strong>. A confirmation dialog shows the credentials to be deleted before you confirm. You can also select all visible credentials using the checkbox in the table header.</p>

<h4>Reveal Clear Password</h4>
<p>Click the eye icon in the Password column to display the plain-text password in a modal dialog.</p>

<h4>Filter Credentials</h4>
<p>Type in the filter box at the top of the table to narrow results by username, realm, or app. The filter is case-insensitive and updates live as you type.</p>

<h2>Using Stored Passwords</h2>
<p>See the <a href="https://dev.splunk.com/enterprise/docs/developapps/manageknowledge/secretstorage/">Splunk developer documentation</a> for details on reading stored credentials from your app's Python or JavaScript code.</p>

<h2>Support</h2>
<h3>Feature Requests</h3>
<p>Please <a href="https://github.com/sghaskell/rest-storage-passwords-manager/labels/enhancement">submit feature requests through GitHub</a> using the <code>enhancement</code> label.</p>
<h3>Bugs</h3>
<p>Please <a href="https://github.com/sghaskell/rest-storage-passwords-manager/labels/bug">submit bugs through GitHub</a> using the <code>bug</code> label.</p>
<h6><a href="https://github.com/sghaskell/rest-storage-passwords-manager">Code hosted at GitHub</a></h6></html>
  </row>
</dashboard>
